{
    "id": "3c4002a259be4e0ab753b074656f58ba",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have lived in this city ……………………… fifteen years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3dc9a01f81844185b27bd0b7d300999c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has not …………………. returned from school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "just"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "167b712983414e1c9daad9f3e27f384a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane has …………………. gone out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "943525b97c724452a39e89310168bb14"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have not returned my money …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5133e08abc8b4034a8a50788cabf5a3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "James has ………………….. arrived in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00d96c3df28748a5aee98d647f6e46bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………….. had a call from your mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f612d642d3ad4e17bf1fbca0f8a80e86"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has worked with me ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab32b6d0274243868c37d1c2a6ff632b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him …………………. two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9040012259c44d418a5486c0f5dce609"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ...................................... have you known him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6be8916defa42d9ba2d98790d4343d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ................................ completed my homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3502b0a527cc4885917a04ea40a5182d"
        }
    ]
}